An auto driver goes out early in the morning to
guide others to their destination. Be it rain
or storm, he is not worried about himself. He just works hard to earn his daily
bread.
He has to work for 12 hours a day.
His auto is either on installment or is
taken on lease from some businessman. The responsibility of the house is so
big that he does
not even realize when morning turns into evening and evening turns into night. In
this way, days pass by and months turn into years.
After 20-25 years, the
auto driver is left with no respite in his old age.
Then neither his income nor
clouds remain and his health has also deteriorated.
If he has saved money in his old age, then
that is his biggest support.
If the hands that have always given him, do not want to beg in front of anyone in his old age, then
invest in a savings scheme of Link today.
What would you like in the future? Will you
drive the auto all your life or will people
drive the auto for you? Don't rely on God, who
knows, God might be relying on you.